Utopia is a mystery, thriller, action film directed by James Bamford.
A soldier searching for his missing wife breaks into a high-tech facility,
believing she's been caught in a human trafficking ring.
But beyond its walls, he finds a surreal, futuristic
fantasy park where reality and illusion blur.
As he navigates this seductive and dangerous world, a shocking truth pulls
him deeper into a deadly game where nothing is as it seems.
Damon, played by Moe Dunford.
Alexis, played by Charlotte Vega.
Jeremy Zenner, played by Michael D. Xavier.
Joan, played by Wanda Banda.
Utopia is a 2024 American cyber thriller action film directed by
James Bamford and written by Ian Neligh and Steven Paul.
The film stars Moe Dunford, Charlotte Vega, Daniel Bernhardt, and Philipp Boos.
It was released on December 10, 2024, by Republic
Pictures via Paramount Pictures for streaming.
The film explores themes of human trafficking, dangerous
mission, cyber thriller, deadly game, missing wife.
The tone is intense and thought_provoking and mind_bending.